Companion NPCs - Alpha Build 0.0.1

Companion NPC's allows you to recruit any of the Bachelors or Bachelorettes to be 
your traveling companion! To recruit them, a farmer must have at least 6 friendship
hearts with them and exhaust their daily dialogue. In addition to following you 
throughout the map, companions also:

+Have unique location-specific dialogue in many parts of the map.
+Grant buffs and (sometimes) perks according to the table below:

﻿Companion 		﻿﻿Buffs﻿				Perk
Abigail 		+1 Speed. +1 Luck. +10% Attack﻿﻿  -
Alex﻿﻿﻿      		+20% Attack﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿    			100% Warrior Ring effect
Elliott﻿﻿﻿   		+3 Fishing﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿			-
Emily﻿﻿﻿    		+2 Mining﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿			100% Yoba Ring effect after damage. Heals you rapidly when <40% health.
Haley﻿﻿﻿    		+3 Luck﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿    			-
Harvey﻿﻿﻿  		+10 Defense﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿    			Heals you slowly when <80% health.
Leah﻿﻿﻿     		+3 Foraging﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿      		-
Maru﻿﻿﻿    		+1 Any Stat﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿      		Buffed stat is interchangeable
Penny﻿﻿﻿   		+3 Farming﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿      		-
Sam﻿﻿﻿     		+2 Speed﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿  			-
Sebastian﻿﻿     		Same as Abigail﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿      		-
Shane﻿﻿﻿   		+3 Farming﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿﻿      		-

For the sake of realism, every NPC is only allowed to hang out on certain days be default.
These dates can be changed via the config.json file in this version for testing purposes though.
By default, the days are:

Mon	|Tue	|Wed	|Thu	|Fri	|Sat	|Sun
------------------------------------------------------
Penny	Sam	Abi	Leah	Alex	Elliott	Emily
	Seb	Maru		Haley	Harvey	Shane

*** Note that this is an Alpha build, meant to showcase the concept and for bug-testing ***
If you're feeling like a real cool dude, you can help my development process by reporting 
bugs in the posts, or via this google doc: https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CuWcGd0VVDreF9TR_gR1GPHpDwF-dh12mA7rqhO78tM/edit?usp=sharing﻿.

+Installing & Usage:
Make sure the latest version of SMAPI is installed
Download this mod from the files tab and unzip it into your Stardew Valley/Mods folder
Run the game using SMAPI

+Compatability:
Works on Windows 10, SDV version 1.3.32. I haven't tested it on Mac, Linux, or Ubuntu so let me know if it isn't working for you on one of those OS' and I'll mess around with the build settings.
No known compatibility issues with other mods.